<idea-plugin>
    <id>alibabacloud.developer.toolkit</id>
    <name>Alibaba Cloud Developer Toolkit</name>
    <vendor email="sdk-team@alibabacloud.com" url="https://www.aliyun.com">AlibabaCloud</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
<p>
  The Alibaba Cloud Developer Toolkit for JetBrains makes it easier to access Alibaba Cloud services.
</p>
<h2><strong>Features:</strong></h2>
<ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Profile Configuration:</strong> Support switch and edit user profile through static credentials, which
    is consistent with Alibaba Cloud CLI. The status bar located at the bottom of the IDE displays the current
    profile. <a href="https://help.aliyun.com/document_detail/123181.html?spm=a2c4g.121544.0.0.2d7e76e3XWMs4u">Learn
    more about CLI Configuration</a>
    <br>
    <ul>
      <li>
        If you have already installed Alibaba Cloud CLI, you can switch your existing profiles. You can open the
        config.json configuration file by clicking "Edit Profile" to further edit user profiles.
      </li>
      <li>
        If you don't have Alibaba Cloud CLI installed, this plugin can automatically create a config file for
        you and provide a default empty configuration.
      </li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>
    <strong>Product Explorer:</strong> A tree-view of cloud products with search: Quickly navigate you to the corresponding
    products or APIs. You can refresh the product list or API detail page by clicking the refresh button in the window toolbar.
  </li>
  <li>
    <strong>API Document View:</strong> Clicking on an API can navigate you to a new tab which displays the corresponding API document,
  including descriptions, request parameters, response parameters and error codes. With cache implemented, subsequent
  visits to the same API will be loaded swiftly.
  </li>
  <li>
    <strong>API Debug (Beta):</strong> Support convenient API debugging within the IDE against the parameter list, and
    also offers a "Go Debug" button for seamless transition to debug in browser.
  </li>
  <li>
    More features are under development, please stay tuned.
  </li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Installation:</strong></h2>
  You can download the Alibaba Cloud Developer Toolkit for JetBrains by searching for "Alibaba Cloud Developer Toolkit" in the
  JetBrains Marketplace in your IDE, or download installation files from your web browser.
</p>
    ]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="Alibaba Cloud Developer Toolkit"
                    anchor="left"
                    factoryClass="com.alibabacloud.ui.BaseToolWindow"
                    secondary="false"
                    icon="/icons/toolwindow.svg"
        />
        <statusBarWidgetFactory id="AlibabaCloud" implementation="com.alibabacloud.ui.MyStatusBarWidgetFactory"
                                order="after encodingWidget"/>
        <notificationGroup id="AlibabaCloud API: Warning" displayType="BALLOON"/>
        <notificationGroup id="AlibabaCloud API: Error" displayType="BALLOON"/>
    </extensions>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="alibabacloud.cli">

    </extensions>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <b>0.0.1 (2023-12-12)</b>
      <ul>
        <li>Alpha version.</li>
        <li>Provides static credentials for switch and edit user profiles.</li>
        <li>Provides product explorer and API document view.</li>
      </ul>
      <b>0.0.2 (2023-12-27)</b>
      <ul>
        <li>Support refresh operation and loading page.</li>
        <li>Support search products and apis.</li>
        <li>Support api debug capability and optimize api display interface.</li>
        <li>Add cache.</li>
      </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <idea-version since-build="222"/>
</idea-plugin>